Hartford National Corporation Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Merger Banks, undated, 1792-1988
  - Subseries A: Hartford National Corporation, 1792-1988
    - Fidelity Trust Company, 1885-1923
      - Stock certificates, 1907-1920
      - Stock certificates, 1920-1921
    - First National Bank of Hartford, 1864-1949
      - Reports of condition, 1923-1949 (Box 130)
      - Statement of condition, 1903-1924
      - Stock certificates, 1807-1907 (Box 131)
      - Stock certificates, 1916-1927 (Box 132)
      - Stock certificates, 1930-1949 (Box 133)
    - General Bank and Trust Company, 1928-1970
      - Cancelled stock certificates, 1959-1963 (Box 134)
      - Cancelled stock certificates, 1963-1970 (Box 135)
      - Cancelled stock certificates, undated (Box 136)
    - Merchants National Bank, 1833-1928
      - Report of examination, 1927 (Box 137)
      - Stock ledger, 1851 (Box 138)
      - Dividend book, 1853-1866
      - Statement book no. 1, 1851-1854 (Box 139)
      - Transfer book, 1851-1875 (Volume Vol. 11)
      - Bank ledger A, 1856-1864 (Volume Vol. 12)
      - Bank ledger E, 1874-1879 (Volume Vol. 13)
      - Bank ledger F, 1879-1883 (Volume Vol. 14)
    - Middlesex County National Bank, 1830-1955
      - Checks, 1911-1915 (Box 140)
      - Mergers and consolidations, 1915
      - Lease, 1907
    - Middletown National Bank, 1801-1955
      - Correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 141)
      - Deeds and mortgages, 1831-1897
      - Reports of condition, 1945-1955 (Box 142)
      - Tax returns, 1939-1945
      - Record book, 1910-1917 (Box 143)
      - Committee on Trust Affairs and Investments, 1932-1934
      - Discount Committee minutes, 1934-1954
      - Trust committee minutes, 1930-1932
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1930-1933
      - Director's minute books, 1918-1925; (2 vol.)
      - Director's minute books, 1926-1954 (Box 144)
      - Director's weekly minutes, 1931-1943 (Box 145)
    - New London City National Bank, 1807-1953
      - Reports of earnings and dividends, 1924-1944 (Box 146)
      - Reports of condition, 1927-1953
      - Tax returns, 1936-1944 (Box 147)
      - Tax returns, 1945-1952 (Box 148)
    - Pheonix Bank, (814-1954
      - Check book, 1818-1820 (Box 149)
    - Travelers Bank and Trust Company, 1915-1953
      - Condensed statements of condition, 1951-1952 (Box 150)
      - Stock certificates, 1919-1953
    - United States Security Trust Company, 1875-1927
      - By-laws and charter, 1876 (Box 151)
      - Reports of examination, 1924-1926
      - Reports of condition, 1923-1926 (Box 152)
      - Stock certificates, 1872-1886 (Box 153)
      - Stock certificates, 1923-1924
      - Stock certificates, 1875-1891 (Box 154)
      - Reports of condition, 1923-1927 (Box 155)
      - Tax returns, 1923-1926
      - The Story of a Corner, 1926
  - Subseries B: Connecticut National Bank, 1806-1982
    - Atlantic National Bank, 1960-1969
      - List of stockholders, 1963-1969 (Box 156)
      - Report on examination, 1960-1969 (Box 157)
    - City National Bank of South Norwalk, 1882-1963
      - Board minutes, 1882-1958 (Box 158)
      - Exchange of CNBSN stocks for CNB stocks, 1963 (Box 159)
      - List of stockholders, 1958
    - Colony Financial Services Incorporated, 1975-1982
      - Minute book, 1975-1982 (Box 160)
    - Connecticut National Bank, 1831-1921
      - Annual meetings of stockholders, 1907-1918 (Box 161)
      - Checks, 1918-1920
      - Stock certificates, 1878, 1919
    - First Federal Savings and Loan of Meriden, 1936-1971
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1936-1952 (Box 162)
      - Board of Directors mminutes, 1959-1961 (Box 163)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1952-1955
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1962-1966 (Box 164)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1967-1971 (Box 165)
    - First Federal Savings and Loan of Middlesex, 1963-1967
      - Minute book, 1963-1967 (Box 166)
    - First National Bank of Bridgeport, 1864-1909
      - Condensed statements of condition, 1907-1909 (Box 167)
      - Correspondence, 1886
      - Minute book, 1903-1909
      - Record book, 1864-1902
      - Stock certificates, 1866-1893
    - First National Bank and Trust Company of New Haven, 1863-1971
      - Cash Receipts book, 1969-71 (Box 168)
      - Charter Number Two: The Centennial History of the First New Haven National Bank, 1963
      - Executive and Discount Committee, 1920-1935 (Box 169)
      - Loan committee, 1941-1949
      - Record books, 1904-1913
      - Minute books, 1918-1937 (Box 170)
      - Board minutes, 1964-1969 (Box 171)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1941-1968
      - Loan Committee minutes, 1964-1969
      - Executive and Discount Committee, 1957 (Box 172)
      - Loan Committee minutes, 1949-1963
      - Minute book, 1955-1957
      - By-laws and records, 1863-1904 (Box 173)
      - Director's minutes, 1865-1912
      - Stock ledger, undated
      - Dividend book, 1919-1923 (Box 174)
      - Framed photographs of bank, undated (Box 175)
      - Deposit ledger A, 1863-1866 (Volume Vol. 15)
      - Stock ledger with index, 1857-1911 (Volume Vol. 16)
    - First National Bank in Westport, 1852-1954
      - Annual meeting of stockholders, 1933-1954 (Box 176)
      - Report on examination, undated
      - Meetings of directors, 1937-1952 (Box 177)
      - Meetings of directors, 1952-1954
    - First National Company, 1929-1934
      - Certificates of incorporation and organization, 1929 (Box 178)
      - Mergers and consolidations, 1934
      - Stockholders minutes, 1929-1931
    - Fitchburg Bank and Trust Company, 1914
      - Seal, 1914 (Box 179)
    - Fourth Meriden Mutual Building and Loan Association, 1900-1932
      - Board minutes, 1900-1913 (Box 180)
      - Record book, 1923-1932
    - Home Bank and Trust Company, 1854-1971
      - Board minutes, 1855-1965 (Box 181)
      - Board minutes, 1950-1966 (Box 182)
      - Board minutes, 1966-1971 (Box 183)
    - Lexington Trust Company, 1918-1960
      - Stock certificates, 1918-1929 (Box 184)
      - Stock certificates, 1940,1960
      - Stock ledger, 1936-1945
    - National Bank of Commerce, undated, 1877-1889
      - Bank deposit slips, undated (Box 185)
      - Records of deposits, 1877-1879 (Volume Vol. 17)
      - Dealers accounts (oversize), 1887-1889 (Volume Vol. 18)
    - Newfield Bank and Trust Company, 1918-1931
      - Checks, 1925-1938 (Box 186)
      - Report of condition, 1922-1930
      - Report on examination, 1923-2196
      - Deposit certificates, 1925-1931 (Box 187)
      - Incorporator's meetings, 1918-1931
      - Reports of liquidation, 1952 (Box 187)
    - North Haven National Bank, 1964-1976
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1964-1976 (Box 188)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1965-1976
    - Pequonnock National Bank, 1851-1913
      - Checks, 1865-1913 (Box 189)
      - Director's minutes, 1911-1913
      - Report on Examination, 1911
      - By-laws, 1912
      - Stock certificates, 1902-1906
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1851-1913 (Box 190)
      - Deposit records, 1865-1913 (Box 191)
    - Permanent Savings and Loan Association, 1888-1983
      - Articles of agreement, 1888 (Box 192)
      - Cancelled and blank checks, 1905-1907
      - General assembly meetings, 1889-1902
      - Resolution and rules, 1902-1907
      - Financial Committee meetings, 1934-1983 (Box 193)
      - Seal, undated
    - Quinnipiack Bank, 1852-1865
      - Articles of association, 1853-1866 (Box 194)
      - Board minutes, 1853-1865
    - Savings Bank of New London, 1827-1977
      - Savings Bank of New London at 150 Years, 1977 (Box 195)
    - Second National Bank of New Haven, undated
      - 100th anniversary materials, undated (Box 196)
    - Shelton Trust Company, 1921-1950
      - Report on examination, 1950
    - South End Bank and Trust Company, 1929-1963
      - Statements of condition, 1956-1963 (Box 198)
      - Stockholders meetings, 1951-1963
    - Travelers Bank and Trust Company, 1913-1954
      - Statements of condition, 1951-1953 (Box 199)
    - Wallingford Savings and Loan Association, 1916-1959
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1949-1959 (Box 200)
    - Waterbury Trust Company, 1907-1957
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1907-1938 (Box 201)
      - Stockholders minutes, 1907-1938
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1938-1958 (Box 202)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1911-1943 (Box 203)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1943-1957
    - Yale National Bank of New Haven, 1864-1918
      - Directors minutes, 1864-1897 (Box 204)
    - Scrapbooks of Various Banks, 1914-1949 (Volume Vol. 19 - 20)
    - Unidentified Account Records, Volumes and items (Box 205)
      - Day book, 1864-1870 (Box 206)
      - Account book, 1879-1880
      - Repair book, 1880-1881
      - Inventory, 1922
      - Directors meetings, 1935-1949
      - Bank ledger, 1852-1857 (Volume Vol. 21)
      - Trial balance sheet, 1880-81 (Volume Vol. 22)
      - Debit book, 1899 (Volume Vol. 23)
      - Cash book, 1899-1906 (Volume Vol. 24)
      - Debit/credit book, 1927 (Volume Vol. 25)
      - Trial balance sheet, 1939-1940 (Volume Vol. 26)
      - Indexes, undated (Volume Vol. 27-29)
      - Rationing Scale, undated
      - Framed portrait of president William Erving, 1917-1925 (Oversize OS)
      - Framed portrait of president George A. Burt, 1925-1934 (Oversize OS)